lbbhost.com 2012-12-13

# WebTV - MSNTV Hosting, LOWEST PRICES, NO LOST FILES & RELIABLE WebTV Hosting

**Webbywarehouse Privacy Policy.**

**Introduction.**

Webbywarehouse is committed to respecting your online privacy and recognizes your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information, "Personal Information", you share with us.

We have established this Online Privacy Policy so that you can understand the care with which we use to protect your privacy, identity, and information.

Personal Information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address and an email address or other contact information, whether at work or at home. Webbywarehouse only requires and obtains that information which is essential for us to reasonabily verify and validate those individuals who seek to use the services we provide.  We make reasonable attempts to verify the information of each member to ensure the best service possible to all members.

Webbywarehouse will make every reasonable attempt to comply with all State and Federal laws that protect your privacy.  We do not share any information with any other company(s), individual(s), group(s), entity(s), organization(s), or agency(s).  We will comply with any and all legal court orders that would require us to provide information, to the extent that such an order (i.e. subpenoa) is defined.  Short of a legal court order however, we do not share any member information under any circumstances. 

Top of Page

**Cookies and Other Tracking Methods**

Webbywarehouse uses Cookies and Sessions to authenticate members who login to their Webbywarehouse accounts, email accounts, and other Web Features offered by Webbywarehouse.

In some cases Cookies are required to be enabled and properly functioning to gain access to our services.  In those cases if there is a problem with Cookies, it is possible that access to our services may be denied.  The purpose of using Cookies in combination with Session controls, is to provide superior security.  It is through a combination of md5 encrypted Sessions and encrypted Session Cookies, that we can provide the most secure authentication and access for our members.

Webbywarehouse does not gather or track members web activities within Webbywarehouse, or otherwise, via Cookies.  We use Cookies soley for security and privacy purposes.

Top of Page

**Your Choice.**

Webbywarehouse does require members to provide accurate information when signing up for an account, or in any manner using any of our services where a username and/or password is or may be required.  In any cases where information is either required or optional, we require the information that is provided to be accurate and complete.  If we find that any information is not valid and/or accurate, then Webbywarehouse has the right to take any appropriate action to protect it's members, it's networks, it's servers, and all other assetts.

Top of Page

**Security.**

Wherever your Personal Information may be held within Webbywarehouse, we take reasonable and appropriate steps to protect the Personal Information that you share with us from unauthorized access or disclosure.

Top of Page

**Access and Accuracy.**

To the extent that you do provide us with Personal Information, Webbywarehouse wishes to maintain accurate Personal Information. Where we collect Personal Information from you on the Web, our goal is to provide a means of contacting us should you need to update or correct that Information. If for any reason those means are unavailable or inaccessible, you may send updates and corrections about your Personal Information to [info@webbywarehouse.com](mailto:info@webbywarehouse.com) and we will make reasonable efforts to incorporate the changes in your Personal Information that we hold as soon as practicable. 

Top of Page

**Third Party Services**.

Webbywarehouse does not provide any information to any third parties who we may link to, associate in any way with, or use the services of.  Webbywarehouse will not, under any circumstances, share any personal information to any other party.

Top of Page

**Children's Privacy.**

Webbywarehouse is not structured to attract children. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect Personal Information from anyone we know to be under 13 years of age.   In the cases where children have an account with Webbywarehouse, we require the consent of a parent or legal guardian.  Webbywarehouse does not permit any adult or illegal content.  Should any such content, or any other content that is not acceptable as defined in our Terms of Service Agreement be discovered, we will take all appropriate actions to remove such material.  Webbywarehouse is a "Family Friendly" and moral host.

Top of Page

**Commitment.**

We are committed to privacy and, through our membership in the Online Privacy Alliance, are actively involved in and support current industry initiatives to preserve individual privacy rights on the Internet. Protecting your privacy online is an evolving area, and Webbywarehouse's Web sites are constantly evolving to meet these demands.

If you have any comments or questions regarding our Online Privacy Policy, please contact us at [info@webbywarehouse.com](mailto:info@webbywarehouse.com) . While we cannot guarantee privacy perfection, we will address any issue to the best of our abilities as soon as possible. 

**Your Consent.**

By using this Web site, you consent to the terms of our Privacy Policy and to Webbywarehouse's processing of Personal Information for the purposes given above as well as those explained where Webbywarehouse collects Personal Information on the Web. Should the Online Privacy Policy change, we intend to take every reasonable step to ensure that these changes are brought to your attention by posting all changes prominently on our web site for a reasonable period of time.

Top of Page
